{
    "subject": "resource/Laza_Ristovski",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfDeath",
    "object": "resource/Belgrade",
    "human_readable": "Laza Ristovski died in Belgrade.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.907183825969696,
            "question": "Was Laza Ristovski born in Belgrade?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.843934178352356,
            "question": "Where did Laza Ristovski die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7968517541885376,
            "question": "When did Laza Ristovski die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47764065861701965,
            "question": "What is Laza Ristovski remembered for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43455323576927185,
            "question": "Was Laza Ristovski a famous person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34400713443756104,
            "question": "What is Laza Ristovski known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3271826505661011,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Laza Ristovski's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31872954964637756,
            "question": "What was Laza Ristovski's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2741122543811798,
            "question": "Is there any information about Laza Ristovski's accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23075085878372192,
            "question": "Do you have any information about Laza Ristovski's family?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Laza Ristovski died in Belgrade.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1052_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information about Laza Ristovski's accomplishments?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1052_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Laza Ristovski's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1052_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Laza Ristovski's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1052_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1052_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1052_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1052_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1052_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1052_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1052_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1052_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1052_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1052_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1052_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information that supports the statement \"Laza Ristovski died in Belgrade.\" Specifically, the document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1052/re-ranker-msmarco/22.txt states \"He died on 6 October 2007 in Belgrade, Serbia,\" which aligns with the given query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}